Welcome back, friends.
Why can’t you just leave me alone?
Bean, running from your mother
is so last year.
Elfo’s more of a mother to me
than you.
This ruins so many fantasies,
but opens up so many new ones.
Announcing the return
of Princess Tiabeanie.
Warning. She appears to be
in a bit of a mood.
Ow!
There are people inside this castle
who want me dead.
She is clearly a threat.
Elfo and Luci are all I have
and that is not a deep bench.
We gotta get out of here.
Damn it!
Woah, Steamland.
There’s a power in Dreamland
beyond anything we have here.
I’m offering an alliance
between magic and science.
This is big. I really need
some time to drink about this.
-You mean--
-I know what I said.
This is the sinister plot
that just keeps giving.
So much gasping.
Our queen.
I know you can do this.
Badass Bean is the Bean
I wanna see right now.
You’re right. I am badass!
What is this?
Oh, my God. Calm down.
Oh, no, this is your life now.
It’s forever!
All right. I’ll talk to you later.